

CONTACT ME AT



Hochstraße 15B, 13357 Berlin



lauraczerbini@gmail.com



<u>/laurazerbini</u>



<u>/laurazerbini</u>

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- ES6 JavaScript
- · Wireframes, Prototyping, UI Design
- · Git, GitHub, technical workflow
- Relational databases, SQL
- Ruby on Rails
- · APIs, JSON, scraping

SOFT SKILLS

- · Customer driven
- Solutions oriented
- Great communicator
- Fast learner

LANGUAGES

- Brazilian Portuguese [native]
- English [fluent]
- German [working proficiency]
- Spanish [basic]

LAURA ZERBINI

WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a professional with a design background who is working since 2018 in a fintech start-up in Berlin. These past years in the tech scene made me keen to change careers to web development and having concluded a coding bootcamp I look forward to deepen my knowledge ideally working with JS.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Team Lead 2nd Level

Simplesurance GmbH | Sep 2019 - present

- Professional leadership of team of 6-18 people
- Fulfilment of goals & KPIs for service level
- Working in cooperation with BI and finance for data reports

Claim Manager

Simplesurance GmbH | Nov 2018 - Ago 2019

Claims and complaints management for UK and PT market

Brand Environment Specialist

Levi Strauss & Co | Apr 2015 - Jun 2017

- Responsible for retail channel over 70 POS'
- · Briefing and ordering graphic POS stationary
- Established and maintained visual merchandising standards
- Active collaboration to 15+ store openings, resulting in a positive EBIT 2 sears in a row (2015 -> + 8.5% // 2016 -> + 10%)

Visual Merchandising Assistant

Levi Strauss & Co | Apr 2015 - Jun 2017

- · Graphics and translations of POS materials
- · Responsible for productions and freight quotations

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Le Wagon Berlin | Batch 533

24 Weeks Web Development Bootcamp | Jan 2021 - Jun 2021

- 24-week part-time coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails
- Designed, implemented and shipped to production a clone of AirBnB and a Rails prototype of ScrewApp.

SENAC | SP

BA Fashion Design | Jan 2010 - Dec 2013

Relevant modules:

Fashion Draw | Graphic Design | Product Development | Entrepreneurship and Creative Economy | Fashion History